All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
This fight's starting to get super exciting now, huh?
I'd say a 50,000-man brawl is the perfect time to take them for a test drive.
Test drive?
Did you say them? Them who?
The Sunny just got two brand new weapons! Big ones! Do you guys wanna see them?
Yeah! Of course we do!
Three-sword style!
Black rope! Tatsumaki!
This is sick! It's a sword hurricane!
Ryan, you're gonna get caught! How long is this thing gonna last?!
Until you get to hell.
He's gone!
Huh?
Skywalk!
Awesome! Zaji can walk on air now!
Doble Jomber!
Hoala Fear!
Spector!
You can send a hundred thousand or ten million guys after us, but every single one of them is going down, you hear me?!
Unveiled! The Secret Weapons of the Sunny!
This Nineteenth Delight
See what's next for it?
See what else!
Mother is mentioned!
It's almost oh-
Alright, he has to sådan you out, please!
Why is this Чтобы proof of the Sunny lotta the Rain?
What!
It's not impossible
You'll be ruled by...
For if not the Falcon sucks
Like I say this
Ah!
Don't think you can show me up, Mosshead!
Yeah, try to stop me!
This is not a competition.
Just ignore them. They act like this every time.
Man, I was really hoping they'd have grown out of this stupid macho act by now.
As long as everyone's fired up, it's all good.
Time to take them out for a spin.
Now that's what I'm talking about!
Wait, you mean the new weapons?
You know I do! Follow me!
I'm so excited!
Wait up!
Hang on! Don't leave me out here by myself!
You're crowding me!
Then go away!
You've done enough damage! It's time to die!
Shut up!
They're way... too strong!
Huh?
What did you say to me?
The humans are too strong for you?
You call yourself a fish man?
Captain!
I'm sorry, sir! Please!
What kind of soldier whimpers and cries?
What kind of fish man is afraid of humans?
Get out of my side!
Shit.
Didn't I tell all of you to kill Shira Hoshi already?
Yes, Shira Hoshi!
This place is awesome! Nice digs!
Something looks different. What did you do exactly?
There wasn't a five or six before.
She's right! And it looks like Zero's gone now!
I remodeled!
After some serious renovation, I was able to turn Zero into five and six.
Department four used to be empty, but it holds one of the new weapons now.
And the other one is tucked away in number five.
That's enough talking! I want to see the new weapons now!
Keep your pants on, bro!
Though you might need a fresh pair after you lay your eyes on these!
Sweet!
Let's get this over with already!
Artillery alert!
Take aim and kill Shira Hoshi!
Actually, I have a better idea!
How about instead, we leave the world's most lovely mermaid princess alone, huh?
Now here's some party music!
What's going on?
Why'd it get dark?
Welcome all to this festival night!
What the...?
This is...
Amazing!
Well, would you like to dance?
Woof!
I guess...
It was all a dream.
That big fight we were having.
Now, it's time to set up the fireworks!
Woof!
We ain't had as much fun in years!
Ha ha!
Huh?
It's beautiful!
Hey, what the hell are you guys aiming at?
Just kill her!
Uh, yeah, but we can't.
We're enjoying the festival too much.
Cut. Sorry, party's over.
Huh?
Point of tears.
Fantasia.
Ah!
Huh?
Ganging up together to intimidate a poor defenseless princess.
You call yourselves men?
Neil Blue!
Gigantesco Mono!
Legs!
And stop!
Sorry.
There's a lot of screaming going on.
Is that good or bad?
It's way too cramped for us all to be in here.
Then why don't you get out?
You're not even interested in the weapons anyway.
Because if I go outside, I'm going to have to fight.
I don't want to be stuck out there either.
Frankie!
Can we hurry this up a little please?
I can't rush greatness, kid.
But fine.
Let's do this.
Actually, I'm getting pretty excited now too.
That's great, but can you move?
I'm supposed to operate this thing.
It got bigger.
Why couldn't it start out this way?
It's show time!
There ain't nothing stopping this unveiling.
Can't wait!
Yeah, but for what?
Let's rock and roll!
Get him, squad, get in there.
Yeah!
It doesn't matter how big your legs or arms are,
because you ain't gonna be nothing but a dead woman
once we get our stingers in ya house.
Come on, come on.
I can't wait.
Come on, let's go.
All right.
Let's go.
that woman once we get our stingers in ya.
Well, in that case...
Soldier Dark System!
Channel Four!
The door opened up!
There wasn't a chance to destroy your ship!
March Black Rhino!
It's F-R-U-4!
The End
Soldier Dark System!
Channel Four!
March Black Rhino!
It's F-R-U-4!
Whoa!
A motorbike!
So cool!
I want it!
That's one tough machine!
And stylish, too!
Let's see this venom of yours!
He's coming right at us!
You can try stinging it if you really wanna!
But this monster's made of pure steel!
How was that?
On a scale of one to super!
Someone stop that guy!
I got him!
Time for steel on steel!
Just leave it to me, boys!
Come on!
You're not scared, are you?
Huh!
Whoa!
Ah!
The new number, channel 5!
Wracchio-Tank 5 is here!
No way!
A dinosaur, for real!
Give me one, two!
You guys see that perfect shot I made?
Yeah, but I don't think you're using this to its full potential.
Man, and here I thought Frankie was just a ship
Frankie was just a shipwright.
Attention!
Pop tube!
I'm Commander Chopper!
We have enemy bogeys inbound off our nine o'clock!
Fire!
She's so cool!
Hey! You need a fight, too!
This is crazy! I mean, they didn't look this tough.
There's only ten of them, but they're taking on a hundred thousand like it was nothing at all.
Do you think they can pull it off?
I sure hope so. Right now, they're the only hope we have. If they can't save us, no one will.
Go, Straw Hat! Beat those guys! We believe in you!
You're doing great! Keep it up! Just a little more!
When you win, you can eat as much food as you want at my restaurant!
I'll give you free drinks at my bar, too!
Straw Hat!
We're counting on you!
Get him, Jinbei!
This has gone on too long.
Rise! My Kraken!
Huh?
No!
Whoa! It's huge!
You have ten targets. Kill the humans! Go! Crush them! You heard me!
They've got a Kraken? No! That's cheating!
Oh, watch out!
It doesn't matter how strong the Straw Hats are, they're all goners if they get smashed by those giant tentacles!
Yeah, the Kraken always does whatever Captain Ordy tells it to do.
And it's strong as hell!
They don't have a pair against our deepy wrecking ball!
Oh, hey, it's that thing.
What are you waiting for?
Get to it!
Seeing as I'm the one who dragged you here all the way from the North Pole, that makes me your master.
So kill them already!
Or I kill you.
Please, can we talk about this?
Ah!
So, uh, do you think that's the same one?
If there's a whole bunch of those things out there, I don't want to know.
Wait, you guys have met the Kraken before and you're not scared?
I wonder if he's uncomfortable out of the water.
Oh, hey, Tsurumi!
Don't tell me you can't see me down here!
It's Luffy!
Huh?
Stop fooling around!
You wouldn't forget your old pal, right?
Come on, you were my pet for a while!
You and I are buddies!
I think we're about to get pounded!
All right, he learned his lesson!
Enough!
Good boy!
No kidding.
And you tamed the Kraken just like you said.
I thought you were nuts!
Yeah!
If that goopy dude can have a sea monster pull his ship, then we can have Tsurumi pull the Sunny!
Right, pal?
Let me ride on you again!
We found him!
Luffy, no!
Huh?
That's Nichols!
Hey, knock it off, Tsurumi!
Yeah!
All righty!
Let's get moving!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
The Kraken has betrayed us!
The Kraken!
Knock it off!
Get the super octopus!
Ah!
Crush up!
All righty!
Uh!
Captain!
Help!
Me!
Go that way, buddy!
Dammit!
What's going on?
It's doing everything Strawhead says!
But why?
Why?
Listen up, Tsurumi!
I want you to stay here and protect Weepy Hoshi!
I can't believe you managed to ingratiate yourself to the Kraken.
It seems no matter where you go, you always befriend the highest caliber allies.
Think so?
Um...
Thank you very much for lending us your power, Tsurumi!
Ha ha ha ha!
Huh?
There's still a lot of these guys left!
All right!
Bring it on!
Thank you so much!
Frankie's weapons find a surprising foe in Hordy's tiniest follower, Daruma.
Setting a trap for the rampaging Straw Hats, the new Fishman Pirates take command of the battlefield.
However, Chopper and Frankie's mechanical masterpiece both have transformations in store that can only be described as super.
On the next One Piece, Iron Pirate, here comes General Frankie! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Happy Mad to chase you next time!
Class!
Last one day.